Constantin Razvan

Entry Web Developer





+40731818905



Romania



razvanccst@gmail.com



https://rc-portofolio.netlify.app/

SKILLS

COMMUNICATION

CREATIVITY

PROBLEM- SOLVING

PLANNING AND ORGANISING

PROFILE

I am an **Entry Web Developer** searching for a fixed position in a modern company where I can utilize my creative, organizational and management skills to drive growth. My previous experience as a manager and coordinator of various projects with world-renowned Video Production companies taught me to always be aware of changes and needs that may arise, and take on new responsibilities as they come. I am a "people person" and enjoy working in a fast-paced environment by staying calm under pressure.

HARD SKILLS

HTML/CSS, Javascript, ReactJS, NodeJS, Ecma Script 6, Web Services API, MySQL, MongoDB, NPM Scripts, Model-View-Controller,

PROJECTS

React Expense Tracking APP

https://rc-react-expense-tracking.netlify.app

Recipe Application - Javascript

https://github.com/razvanccst/Recipe-Application

Mapty - Geolocation Application - Javascript

https://mapty-geolocation.netlify.app

Bank App - Presentation Website - Javascript

https://rc-presentation-bank-app.netlify.app

Bank Application - Javascript

https://rc-bank-application.netlify.app

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Informatics

Faculty of Mathematics and Informatics, Ovidius University Constanta 2012 - 2015

LANGUAGES

Romanian

Motherlanguage

English

Advanced Writting / Speaking

Spanish

Basic Writing / Speaking

INTERESTS



Programming



Video



Travelling

COURSES

React – The Complete
Guide(Hooks, React Router, Redux)

Javascript Course 2022: from 0 to Expert

The Complete 2022 Web Developer Bootcamp

WORK EXPERIENCE

TV Production Manager

Casa Iubirii / Kanal D / Bucharest / 01.03.2022-01.06.2022

Executive Producer

Fara Filtre Podcast / AllMates Production / 01.08.2021-28.02.2022

TV Production Coordinator

Survivor Romania / Acun Medya / Dominican Republic / 01.12.2020-15.07.2021

TV Production Coordinator

The Batchelor / Antena Group / Istanbul / 01.06.2020-01.11.2020

TV Production Assistant

Survivor Romania / Acun Medya / Dominican Republic / 01.12.2019-01.06.2020

Bussiness Analyst

Telekom Romania / Bucharest / 01.01.2018 - 01.09.2018

Marketing Assistant

ASUS Romania / Bucharest / 01.02.2016 - 30.12.2017